no changes to save. Yeah. So whenever that we're using the image editor of Microsoft designer,
the point here is that at first, so first of all, it asks us to upload our image, you know,
because when it comes to editing, we already have something that we want to edit, right?
So first of all, it asks us to upload our image. We can close this window so we can skip this part
and get straight into the editor itself, but we can also use that window, which was opened,
in order to upload our images. So now that I've closed that one, how do I add an image?
So how do I get back to uploading image? I can click on add image over here. So in the edit tab,
by clicking on add image and by clicking on my media. Yes.
So I click on upload from this device and I come to, yeah, I come here and I click on this image
for retouching purposes, right? That's what I'm looking for. But right now, I'll just wait until the
image is added into the editor.